awspartner.com 2016-12-22

# AWS Privacy

Amazon Web Services, Inc. (“AWS”) knows that you care how your information is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly.  

**What is covered by this Privacy Policy:**

This AWS Privacy Policy describes how we collect and use information that customers provide to us in connection with the creation or administration of AWS accounts, which we refer to as “Account Information”. For example, Account Information includes names, usernames, phone numbers, email addresses and billing information associated with a customer’s AWS account.

This AWS Privacy Policy applies to customers’ Account Information and does not apply to the content that customers store on our system, including any personal information of their end users. AWS will not disclose, move, access or use customer content except as provided in the customer’s agreement with AWS. See your agreement with AWS and the [AWS Data Protection FAQ](https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/data-privacy-faq/) for more information about how we handle content you store on our systems.

**How AWS uses Account Information:**

AWS is a subsidiary of Amazon.com, Inc. or its affiliates (“Amazon.com”). As a subsidiary of Amazon.com, AWS follows the same information practices as Amazon.com, and Account Information we collect is subject to the Amazon.com [ Privacy Notice](http://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496). By visiting the AWS site, you are accepting the practices described in the Amazon.com [ Privacy Notice](http://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496). Please note that, if you have an account on [www.amazon.com](http://www.amazon.com/) and an Amazon.com cookie, Account Information gathered by AWS, may be correlated with any personally identifiable information that Amazon.com has and used by AWS and Amazon.com to improve the services we offer.

**EU-US Privacy Shield**

AWS participates in the EU-US Privacy Shield framework. Click [here](http://www.amazon.com/privacy) to learn more.

_Last Updated September 30, 2016_
